{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019. The Patriots lost to the Dolphins 27-20.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019. The Patriots lost 27-20.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019. The Patriots lost 27-20.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2013.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2013",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2013",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on November 24, 2019. The Patriots won the game 27-20.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2013.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019, the Patriots defeated the Dolphins 43-0.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "12/20/2015",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "12/12/2022",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "12/20/2015",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "12/12/2022",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2024",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 1974",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/19/2017",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "12/12/2022",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "12/12/2021",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "11/24/2019",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 25, 2018.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 25, 2018.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 25, 2018.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 21, 2021.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 20, 2024",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 23, 2024",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "November 24, 2024",
      "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ]
}